Hill, James C. Arbitration Files 5538
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II - Arbitration Files
  - Sub-Series B. Arbitration Files
    - Supermarket Operating Company vs. Retail Food Clerks Union, Local 1500, 1963 (Box 117, Folder 9)
      12/21/1963; Issues: Termination; Quits.
    - Sylvania Electric Products, Inc. vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 511, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 10)
      5/15/1964; Grievance #172 Case #L-39171 SYR-L-71-63 Issues: Layoffs; Testing.
    - Taylor Business Institute vs. United Federation of College Teachers, Local 1460, 1974 (Box 117, Folder 11)
      3/22/1974; #1330-1073-73 Issue: Compensation.
    - Tenneco Chemicals, Inc. vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 801, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 12)
      11/29/1973; Issues: Employee Rights; Holidays and Holiday Pay; Bargaining History.
    - Texaco Inc., Marine Department vs. National Maritime Union of America (NMU), 1961 (Box 117, Folder 13)
      ca. 1/61; Arbitration Award Not Included.
    - Texaco Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-688, 1965 (Box 117, Folder 14)
      1/15/1965; Issues: Suspension; Plant Rules.
    - Texaco Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1965 (Box 117, Folder 15)
      11/26/1965; Issues: Suspension; Absences.
    - Texaco Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1970 (Box 117, Folder 16)
      4/1/1970; Issues: Suspension; Theft.
    - Thatcher Glass Manufacturing Company vs. Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 1)
      6/13/75. Grievance #255- 74-121 Issues: Termination of Employment; Negligence and Carelessness.
    - The Thomas and Betts Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1068, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      6/18/71; Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service File #71A/1296 Issues: Suspension; Insubordination; Improper Personal Conduct.
    - Thomasset Colors, Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 13-406, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      7/10/61; Issues: Discharge; Negligence and Carelessness.
    - Thomasset Colors, Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-406, 1965 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      9/30/65; #69A/1024 Settled.
    - Torrington Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1645, 1958 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      Dec. 58; #L-22775- HART-175-58 Issues: Discharge; Absences.
    - Torrington Company vs. Metal Products Workers Union, Local 1645, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 6-11)
      5/11/67; #L-46119-HART-L-100-65 Issue: Contract Negotiations.
    - Torrington Company vs. Metal Products Workers Union, Local 1645, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1969 (Box 118, Folder 12)
      2/24/69; #12-30-0068-68 Issue: Compensation.
    - Torrington Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 13)
      12/26/1972; #12-30-0045-72 Settled.
    - Torrington Company vs. Metal Products Workers Union, Local 1645, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 14)
      10/9/1973; #12-30-0011-73 Settled.
    - Trane Company vs. United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry, Local 730, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 1)
      10/16/1972; Issues: Leaves of Absence; Inability to Work.
    - Treadwell Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1251, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 2)
      2/22/1973; #12-30- 0147-72 Issues: Discipline; Plant Rules; Improper Personal Conduct.
    - Treadwell Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1251, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 3-4)
      5/24/73; #12-30- 0190-72 U.S. District Court #H-74-152 Issue: Back Pay Award.
    - Treadwell Corporation vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1251, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 5)
      5/30/73; #12-30-0146- 72 Grievance #'s 31 and 40 Issues: Suspension; Discharge; Insubordination.
    - Triangle Publications, Inc. vs. Television Broadcasting Studio Employees, Local 804, International Alliance of Theater Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 1)
      2/10/63; Issues: Reinstatement; Union Representatives and Business.
    - Triangle Publications, Inc. vs. Television Broadcasting Studio Employees, Local 804, International Alliance of Theater Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 2)
      9/16/1964; Issue: Part Time Employees.
    - Triangle Publications, Inc. vs. Television Broadcasting Studio Employees, Local 804, International Alliance of Theater Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 3)
      10/28/1964; #L-43496-PHI-L-450-64 Issues: Discharge; Quits.
    - Triangle Publications, Inc. vs. American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 4)
      3/20/1965; #L-44066 NY-L-776-64 Issues: Termination of Employment; Reduction in Force; Automation.
    - Triangle Publications, Inc. vs. Television Broadcasting Studio Employees, Local 804, International Alliance of Theater Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 5)
      10/6/1967; #14-30-0279-66 Grievance #'s 178 and 179 Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Triangle Publications, Inc. vs. National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1969 (Box 120, Folder 6)
      7/3/1969; #1330-0134-67 Issue: Premium Pay.
    - Triangle Publications, Inc. vs. Newspaper Guild of Greater Philadelphia, 1969 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      8/7/69. no.14-30-0613-68 Issues: Termination of Employment; Training and Trial Periods; Standards of Production.
    - Tube Reducing Corporation vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2583, 1959 (Box 120, Folder 8)
      3/9/59. no.57-JCH-75(F) Issues: Supervisors and Foremen; Crew Size.
    - Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs. Flight Engineers International Association, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 9)
      2/15/63. Withdrawn.
    - Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs. Flight Engineers International Association, 1962 (Box 120, Folder 10)
      5/1/62. Report to the President by the Emergency Board Submitted. Final Arbitration Not Included.
    - Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs. Flight Engineers International Association, 1964 (Box 120, Folder 11)
      4/18/64. Issues: Suspension; Rules.
    - Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1966 (Box 120, Folder 12)
      9/16/66. no.5646 Issue: Seniority.
    - Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1968 (Box 120, Folder 13)
      12/9/68. no.5890 and 5872 Issues: Suspension; Standards of Production.
    - Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs. Marie Churchill, 1972 (Box 120, Folder 14)
      9/9/72. Grievance no.7052 Issue: Bumping.
    - Trans World Airlines, Inc. vs. Dean E. Mathiowetz, 1975 (Box 120, Folder 15)
      7/31/75. Grievance no.0196 Issues: Discharge; Theft; Improper Work Practices.
    - Underwood-Olivetti Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 459, 1959 (Box 120, Folder 16)
      1/26/59. no.L-44834 NY-L- 978-64 Issue: Leaves of Absence.
    - Union Carbide Plastics Company vs. Chemical and Crafts Union, Inc., 1961 (Box 120, Folder 17)
      10/24/61. Issues: Holidays; Holiday Pay.
    - Union Carbide Corporation, Linde Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6789, 1967 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      8/18/67. Grievance no.H-42-65 Issues: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Union Carbide Corporation, Nuclear Division vs. Atomic Trades and Labor Council, 1967 (Box 121, Folder 2)
      12/18/67. Grievance no.PMU-76D Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service File no.66A/3368 Issue: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit.
    - Union Carbide Corporation, Linde Division vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 6789, 1968 (Box 121, Folder 3)
      4/5/68. Grievance no.H-29-65 Contains Information re H-42-65, Box 121, ff 1 Above. Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - Union Carbide Corporation, Chemicals Division vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 656, 1968 (Box 121, Folder 4)
      5/26/68. Grievance no.67-646 Issue: Discipline.
    - Union Carbide Corporation, Chemicals and Plastics Operations Division vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Local 656, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 5)
      2/28/72. Grievance no.71-173 Issues: Suspension; Falsification of Records.
    - Union Hardware Division of Brunswick Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 247, 1966 (Box 121, Folder 6)
      5/10/66. Issue: Call-in.
    - United Press International vs. Commercial Telegraphers Union, 1968 (Box 121, Folder 7)
      2/26/68. Settled.
    - United States Metal Refining Company vs. International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, Local 837, 1961 (Box 121, Folder 8)
      10/31/61. no.L-31296 NY-L- 417-61 Issues: Discharge; Absences.
    - United States Military Academy vs. American Federation of Government Employees, Local 2367, 1971 (Box 121, Folder 9)
      8/23/71. Issues: Promotions; Discrimination; Union Representatives and Business.
    - United States Pipe and Foundry Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2026, 1961 (Box 121, Folder 10)
      1/3/61. no.L-28811-PHI-L-466-60 Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - United States Steel Corporation, American Bridge Division vs. Association of Clerical and Technical Employees, American Bridge Division, 1974 (Box 121, Folder 11)
      7/12/74. no.55-30-0146-73 Issues: Suspension; Insubordination.
    - United States Steel Corporation vs. Association of Clerical and Technical Employees, 1974 (Box 121, Folder 12)
      3/4/74. Case no.53-30-0146-73 Grievance no.AB-A- 73-TCE-3 Issue: Bumping.
    - United States Time Corporation vs. Waterbury Watch Workers, Affiliated Local #24369, 1961 (Box 122, Folder 1)
      3/11/61. no.L-28905 HART-L-184-60 Issue: Transfers.
    - Universal Atlas Cement Division of United States Steel Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 115, 1963 (Box 122, Folder 2)
      7/5/63. no.L-35822 PHI-L-743-62 Grievance no.N-2-62 Issues: Classification of Jobs; Rates of Pay.
    - Universal Atlas Cement Division of United States Steel Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 115, 1963 (Box 122, Folder 3)
      7/12/63. Case no.L-35822 PHI-L-743-62 Grievance no.'s N-7-62, N-8-62, N-9-62 Issues: Elimination of Jobs; Rates of Pay.
    - Universal Atlas Cement Division of United States Steel Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 115, 1964 (Box 122, Folder 4)
      4/21/64. Grievances N-6-63, N-7-63 Issues: Overtime; Premium Pay.
    - Universal Atlas Cement Division of United States Steel Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 139, 1964 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      6/27/64. Grievance 63-2 Issues: Assignment of Work; Bumping.
    - Universal Atlas Cement Division of United States Steel Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 189, 1965 (Box 122, Folder 6)
      3/18/65. Grievance 63-17 Issues: Assignment of New Jobs; Rates of Pay.
    - Universal Atlas Cement Division of United States Steel Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 189, 1965 (Box 122, Folder 7)
      3/20/65. Grievance 64-1 Issue: Testing.
    - Universal Atlas Cement Division of United States Steel Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 115, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 8)
      5/23/69. Withdrawn.
    - Universal Atlas Cement Division of United States Steel Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 189, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 9)
      8/12/69. Grievances UAC H 68-10A and UAC H 68-10B Issue: Contracting Out.
    - Universal Atlas Cement Division of United States Steel Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 189, 1970 (Box 122, Folder 10)
      1/15/70. Grievance UAC-H68-2 Issues: Suspension; Absences; Holidays.
    - Universal Atlas Cement Division of United States Steel Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 189, 1974 (Box 122, Folder 11)
      1/20/74. Grievance UAC-H-73-31 Issues: Promotions; Seniority.
    - Vaucanson Silk Mills, Inc. vs. Textile Workers Union of America, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 1)
      9/10/62. no.L-32709 NY-L-790-61 Issues: Termination of Business; Termination of Employment; Layoffs; Welfare Funds.
    - Vertol Division, The Boeing Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1069, 1966 (Box 123, Folder 2)
      10/4/66. no.14-30-0434-66 Issues: Assignment of Jobs; Seniority.
    - Vertol Division, The Boeing Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1069, 1969 (Box 123, Folder 3)
      4/2/69. no.14-30-0872-68 Issues: Discharge; Insubordination; Safety.
    - Vertol Division, The Boeing Company vs. United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 1069, 1971 (Box 123, Folder 4)
      9/13/71. Case no.14-30-0379-71H Grievance 2-628 Issue: Recall.
    - Vickers, Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1335, 1961 (Box 123, Folder 5)
      1/10/61. no.L-32451 HART-L-213-61 Issues: Discharge; Negligence and Carelessness.
    - Vickers, Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1335, 1963 (Box 123, Folder 6)
      1/26/63. Grievance 171 Issues: Holidays; Holiday Pay.
    - Vickers, Inc. vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1335, 1963 (Box 123, Folder 7)
      6/29/63. Issues: Holidays; Holiday Pay.
    - Vickers, Inc. vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 792, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 8)
      5/17/73. Grievance no.I-145 Hill Withdraws.
    - Vidcraft Television Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 430, 1951 (Box 123, Folder 9)
      2/3/51. Issues: Recall; Reporting Pay.
    - John Vogel, Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 294, 1959 (Box 123, Folder 10)
      7/12/50. Issue: Demotions.
    - Walker Brothers vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local BA-1088, 1961 (Box 123, Folder 11)
      7/5/61. no.L-30324-PHI-L-192-61 Issue: Rates of Pay.
    - Scully Walton, Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 522, 1963 (Box 123, Folder 12)
      9/17/63. Issues: Discharge; Quits; Strikes; Slowdowns; Work Stoppages.
    - Washex Machinery Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists, District Lodge 13, 1961 (Box 123, Folder 13)
      4/14/61. Issues: Holidays; Holiday Pay; Discharge; Absences; Tardiness.
    - Waterbury Farrel, Division of Textron, Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3381, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 14)
      12/30/72. Issue: Standards of Production.
    - Waterbury Farrel, Division of Textron, Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 3381, 1969 (Box 123, Folder 15)
      8/5/69. Settled.
    - Watson Manufacturing Company vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District 65, 1971 (Box 123, Folder 16)
      12/71. Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service File no.714/7720 Withdrawn.
    - Weathervane Inn, Inc. vs. Dining Room Employees Union, Local 1, 1954 (Box 123, Folder 17)
      7/25/54. Issues: Discharge; Improper Work Practices.
    - David Weber Company vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 375, 1969 (Box 123, Folder 18)
      3/19/69. no.14-30-0738-68 Withdrawn.
    - A. Weinfeld and Son vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 169, 1965 (Box 123, Folder 19)
      ca. 12/65. Settled.
    - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 358, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 1)
      10/5/62. no.L-33687-PHI-L-91-62 Issues: Removal of Work from the Bargaining Unit; Contracting Out.
    - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 831, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 2)
      10/18/69. no.31-30-0048-69 Issues: Rates of Pay; Overtime.
    - West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 780, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 3)
      12/4/69. no.31-30-0070-69 Issue: Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
    - Western Kraft East, Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 375, 1971 (Box 124, Folder 4)
      12/2/71. no.14-30-0242-71J Settled.
    - Western Electric Company, Inc. vs. Communication Workers of America, Local 3290, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 5)
      3/5/73. Issues: Discharge; Strikes; Slowdowns; Work Stoppages; Improper Personal Conduct.
    - Western Printing and Lithographing Company vs. Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Local 52, 1962 (Box 124, Folder 6)
      10/5/62. no.L-34084 NY-L-266-62 Issues: Suspension; Negligence and Carelessness.
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Locals 315 and 1581, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 1)
      10/11/60. no.L- 25016 CLE-L-70-59 Issues: Discharge; Insubordination (Refused to Testify Before Committee on Un-American Activities of the House of Representatives).
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1805, 1961 (Box 125, Folder 2)
      5/2/61. no.L-29478 PHI-L-592-60 Grievance no.1472 Issues: Suspension; Grievances and Grievance Procedure.
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 491, 1961 (Box 126, Folder 1)
      5/12/61. no.L-28691 NY-L- 674-60 Issues: Seniority; Reinstatement.
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation vs. Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions, 1962 (Box 126, Folder 2)
      10/18/62. no.L-31706 PIT-L-63-61 Carry Over of 2 Books into Box 127. Issues: Termination of Employment; Standards of Production.
    - Westinghouse Electric Corporation vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 130, 1962 (Box 127, Folder 1)
      10/29/62. no.L-34733-PHI- 373-62 Appeal Grievance no.4481-D Issues: Termination of Employment; Standards of Production.
    - Weston Instruments, Inc. vs. Weston Employees Union, 1973 (Box 127, Folder 2)
      2/26/73. Grievance 5-72 Issues: Suspension; Fraud (Time Cards).
    - WHYY-TV vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 1241, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 3)
      6/7/74. no.14-30-0064-74C Issues: Discharge; Negligence and Carelessness; Improper Work Practices.
    - Wilcolater Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 102, 1961 (Box 127, Folder 4)
      7/29/61. Issue: Layoffs.
    - Winchendon Furniture Company vs. United Furniture Workers of America, Local 154 - 12/9/71. #1130-0414-71 Hill Withdraws., 1971 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Witco Chemical Company, Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, Local 8-360, 1966 (Box 127, Folder 6)
      1/14/66. Issues: Bidding; Promotions; Seniority.
    - X - Ray Manufacturing Company vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, Local 475, 1954 (Box 128, Folder 1)
      9/3/54. Issues: Discharge; Strikes; Slowdowns; Work Stoppages.
    - Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company. (Box 128, Folder 2)
      Contains Correspondence Between Yale and Towne and Mr. Hill on Various Cases.
    - Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1717, 1961 (Box 128, Folder 3)
      Contains Approximately 20 Cases Concerning Various Matters Which Resulted from a Strike ca. 8/61.
    - Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1717, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 4)
      4/25/62 and 7/7/62. Transcripts of 2 Hearings.
    - Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1717, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 5)
      9/4/62. Issues: Recall; Ability.
    - Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1717, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 6)
      9/22/62. Issues: Recall; Ability.
    - Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1717, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 7)
      10/16/62. Issues: Recall; Ability.
    - Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1717 (Box 128, Folder 8)
      No Decision. Issues: Recall; Ability.
    - Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1717, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 9)
      1/21/63. Issues: Recall; Ability.
    - Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1717, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 10)
      1/26/63. Withdrawn. Issues: Recall; Ability.
    - Yale and Towne Manufacturing Company vs. International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1717, 1968 (Box 128, Folder 11)
      1/2/68. Withdrawn. Issues: Recall; Ability.
    - Yale University vs. Federation of University Employees, Local 35, 1970 (Box 128, Folder 12)
      10/1/70. Issues: Discharge; Improper Work Practices; Fights and Altercations.
    - Yeshiva University, Albert Einstein College of Medicine vs. Drug and Hospital Employees Union, Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, Local 1199, 1968 (Box 128, Folder 13)
      8/5/68. no.1330-0303-68 Issues: Employee Rights; Part Time Employees.
    - Young's Rubber Corporation vs. Federal Labor Union 23070, 1949 (Box 128, Folder 14)
      12/20/49. Issue: Layoffs.
- Series III - Emergency Boards
  - Sub-Series A. #152 - Pan American World Airways vs. Transport Workers of America
    - Emergency Board 152. Pan American World Airways vs. Transport Workers of America. (Box 129, Folder All)
      Contains Final Reports of Emergency Boards 144 and 146 (Also re Air Strikes), Transcripts of the Proceedings of Emergency Board 152, and Various Exhibits for 152. See Also Box 107, File Folder 2.
  - Sub-Series B. #159 - Brotherhood of Railway Signalmen [vs. Various National Railway Carriers?]. Emergency Board 159.
    Carriers Represented by the National Railway Labor Conference and the Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers' Conference Committees. National Mediation Board Case #A-6967.
    - Post Hearing Brief for the Carriers, the Parties and the Controversy Before the Commission (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Appearances for the Carriers (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - News clipping (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Exhibits of Brotherhood of Railway Signalmen. (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Index to Carriers' Exhibits. (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Carriers Exhibits (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Proceedings of Third Annual Meeting, Communication and Signal Section (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Briefs for the Brotherhood of Railway Signalmen (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Report to the President, 1964 (Box 132, Folder 4)
      Submitted 4/3/64.
  - Sub-Series C. Board of Inquiry - Republic Aviation.
    - Republic Aviation Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists (and Other Unions) and vs. Republic Lodge 1987, International Association of Machinists., 1962 (Box 133, Folder All)